fastsafepatch.com 2014-02-07

# Vimax Pills

PRIVACY POLICY

We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. That is why we have adopted this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used. We promise that we will take the steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy. The following policies are only in effect for the Web pages, newsletters, discussion lists and opt-in announcement lists owned and operated by us. The following discloses our Privacy Policy.

### What information are you collecting and how are you collecting it?

Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers that serve as that computer's "Internet Protocol" IP address. When a visitor requests a page from any Web site within the our network, our Web servers automatically recognizes that visitor's domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from where you have accessed our site. We use this information to examine our traffic in the aggregate and to investigate misuse of our network, or to cooperate with law enforcement. See also: Will you disclose the information you collect to outside third parties? We do not collect and evaluate this information for specific individuals. Our Web servers do not record e-mail addresses of the visitors.

### What are cookies? 

From time to time, we or its advertisers may send a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other Web sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to identify which areas of our network of Web sites you have visited or customized so the next time you visit, those pages may be readily accessible. Our advertisers may also use cookies to ascertain how many times you have seen an advertisement. We and our advertisers may use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you see on our site. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our Site and other Web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.

### How do you use single-pixel gifs? 

We and our advertisers may use single-pixel gif images, sometimes referred to as web bugs or web beacons, to count Web page accesses and gather some general statistical information. We do not gather personal information through the use of these images. Our advertisers may use single-pixel gifs that can track personal information from cookies that may have been previously placed on a user's computer by an advertiser.

### What information do you collect when I purchase your products? 

The nonpublic personal information ("Personal Information") we collect may include, but is not limited to, your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address. We may use this information in connection with certain aspects of our business. For example, we may use this information to complete your requested transaction or to otherwise manage your relationship with us.

If you use a credit or debit card for any of your purchases, we will collect your credit or debit card information and keep a history of your purchases. We use this information to process your orders and to better assist you when you contact us in the future. When you return previously purchased product or request a refund or exchange, you may be asked to give your name, address, and phone number. We collect this information to help prevent fraud.

We may also use your IP address internally and share it with law enforcement in the event of misuse or criminal activity. See: Will you disclose the information that you collect to outside third parties?

### What other information do you request? 

We may also request your e-mail address or mailing address for the purposes of conducting a survey or to provide additional services such as: subscriptions to e-mail newsletters, announcement lists or information about conferences and trade shows. Whenever we request the identity of a visitor, we will clearly indicate the purpose of the inquiry before the information is requested. We maintain a strict "No-Spam" policy that means that we do not intend to sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third-party without your consent.

We may, from time to time, send e-mail announcing our new products and services. Except as stated above, we will not send you e-mail that you have not agreed to receive. If you choose to supply your postal address in an online form, you may receive mailings from other third party companies.When you enter a contest or other promotion, we may ask for your name, address, and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners.

What information do you collect when I purchase something?   
If you are purchasing something from us, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. This information may also be used by us to notify you of related products and services. Credit card and e-mail information will not be shared or sold to third parties for any purpose without your express permission.

Certain properties use a shopping cart feature that safeguards this information by using industry standard SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encrypted servers. SSL codes the information transferred between you and the server, rendering it unreadable to anyone trying to intercept the information.

Wherever we collect personal information we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page.

### How Your Information Is Used?

We use your personal information primarily to provide you with the products and services you request, and to conduct the business. As permitted by law, we may also share your personal information with select partners with whom we have joint marketing agreements in order to provide you with a variety of products and services. We require these companies to meet privacy standards described below. We may also use your personal information to market or determine your possible interest in products and services we may offer.

### Will you disclose the information you collect to outside third parties? 

We will disclose personal information and/or an IP address when required by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

1) Conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served by us,  
2) Protect and defend the rights or property of our network of sites and related properties, or visitors to our network of sites and related properties, or  
3) Identify persons who may be violating the law, our legal notice and Web site User Agreement, the rights of third parties, or otherwise misusing our network or its related properties,  
4) Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities.

We use reasonable precautions to keep the information disclosed to us secure. We reserve the right to transfer all such information in connection with the sale of all or part of our capital stock or assets. Furthermore, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive the information. We are not responsible for such third party privacy policies or how they treat information about their users.

### Security of Your Information 

We protect the personal information you provide against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, destruction, loss, or misuse. Your personal information is protected by physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards in accordance with federal and state standards. These safeguards include appropriate procedures for access and use of electronic data, provisions for the secure transmission of sensitive personal information on our website, and telephone system authentication procedures. Additionally, we limit access to your personal information only to those of our employees who need your personal information in order to provide products or services to you. When you place orders on our sites, all of your order information, including your card number and delivery address, is transmitted through the Internet using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. SSL technology causes your browser to encrypt your order information before transmitting it to our secure server. SSL technology, an industry standard, is designed to prevent someone other than operators of our Web Site from capturing and viewing your Personal Information. Since any order information you provide to us on our Web Site will be transmitted using a secure connection, if your Web browser cannot support this level of security, you will not be able to order products through our Web Site.

### Who May Use this Web Site? 

Our Web Site is not intended or designed to attract users under the age of 18. We do not collect Personal Information from any person we know to be under the age of 18. If you are under 18, we ask that you not send us any Personal Information.

### Your Right to Opt Out 

Providing us with access to your information permits us to offer you distinct advantages and better service. Using your information helps us tailor product offerings to you and eliminate those that may not interest you.  
However, if you do not want us to use your personal financial information for marketing purposes, you may simply let us know by opting out. If you opt out, we will not use your personal information to notify you of new products or services. It will, however, still be released as permitted or required by law. Please note that we cannot withdraw any previous disclosures made with your authorization.   
To opt out, you may contact us by calling at **1-800-381-8791** or emailing at [support@vimaxgroup.com](mailto:support@vimaxgroup.com)  
You may also send us letter to:  
 **Rex Marketing SRL SA, 177 Main Street, PO BOX 3169, PMB257, Road Town, Tortola, British Virgin Islands  
**

## Our Privacy Statement and Outside Links 

This Privacy Statement only applies to websites owned and controlled by Izef llc. Our Web Site may include links to the websites of our business partners, vendors and advertisers. These other sites are outside of our control. Please be aware that these websites may collect information about you, and operate according to their own privacy practices which may differ from those contained in our Privacy Statement. Remember to consult that website's own privacy policy, as once you are outside any of the Web Sites, any information you submit is no longer in our control.

## Changes in Our Privacy Policy 

We may periodically review our policies. We reserve the right to amend them. If we amend this Privacy Policy, we will continue our commitment to maintaining the security and privacy of your personal information.

## What else should I know about my privacy when online? 

Your Consent To This Agreement. By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of information as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
